Graham Harper

harper.grahams@gmail.com | 719.649.4491 | Marina Del Rey, CA

Objective

Highly motivated software engineer seeking employment in a professional environment where I can utilize my passions for cyber security, exploring new technologies, and problem solving. Hoping to build upon the skills I have acquired as a developer for a cyber security training platform as well 5 years of providing technical support for education institutions.

Education

Bachelor's of Computer Science, University of Colorado, Boulder

May 2020

Skills

- Proficient with C++, Python, C, HTML, Git, x86 Assembly
- Competent with Kali tools such as Metasploit, Nmap, Nessus, Wireshark, Autopsy
- Experience implementing functions, writing unit tests, and pushing code within an Agile production system
- Experience working in a Virtual Machine, and sandboxing
- Proficient with Linux (Ubuntu, Kali), and Command Line

Relevant Experience

Cyber Security Software Development Intern

May 2018 - August 2018

Circadence Corporation, 1900 9th St, Suite 200, Boulder, CO

- Collaborated with other software developers to implement offensive and defensive cyber security tools
- Coordinated with a team to coordinate tasks, utilizing agile development methodology, participated in scrums for daily/weekly sprint planning
- Wrote functions and unit tests in python, implementing Kali Linux tools such as Metasploit, Nmap, Wireshark and more
- Learned how to work within an existing system adding to and maintaining an established code base.
- Carried out remote exploitation of target machines

Technology Technician

September 2020 - July 2021

Fountain School District 8, 10665 Jimmy Camp Road, Fountain, CO 80817

- Perform on-site analysis, and resolves complex computer problems for a variety of end-users, and recommends and implements corrective hardware solutions, including off-site repair as needed
- Install, configure, test, and maintain computer hardware, software and peripheral devices

Tuition Classification Student Assistant

August 2016 - May 2020

University of Colorado Boulder, Office of the Registrar, Boulder, CO

- Collaborated in office setting assisting full time staff with Tuition Classification and other duties
- Responsible for answering tuition classification calls, processing in-state residency petitions, handling data entry into University's information system
- In charge of updating documentation on the Registrar's wiki using the wiki-syntax text tiki
- Handled sensitive information and maintain thorough understanding of FERPA and legal responsibilities to protect student information

Graduate School Student Assistant

September 2018 - May 2020

University of Colorado Boulder, Graduate School, Boulder CO

- Assisted with administrative duties in the office of the Dean at the Graduate School
- Handled sensitive student data, requiring attention to detail and extreme discretion

Activities

- UCCS Cyber Security Club member, and CU Ethical Hacking Club member
- Attended Hack CU III(2017) Hackathon, cyberBuffs Hackathon(2018), Hack CU IV(2018)